as we go to our next game point of no
return point of no
return life is a journey full of
wondrous Milestones like a baby's first
steps a child's first kiss jacking off
to the DVD box of your mom's workout
video hearing the garage door open and
desperately wiping off the DVD before
she gets back from the grocery store and
crying cuz you don't know what's
happening to your body and then
eventually getting married and having a
family of your own so while Universal
experiences like those come at different
times for different people thrillist has
compiled the list of things we should
stop doing at certain ages like age3
stop sucking your thumb all right age 25
stop working for free age 33 stop crying
at work
but I'm sure some3
33 33 is to cut off they give you a long
PR far yeah that's a long time so great
it's 35 in New
Jersey I'm sure some were left off the
list so I'd like you to give me some
other things you should have gotten over
by a certain age in 60 seconds and begin
Randazzo age 20 stop marrying Hugh
Hefner points hman age 49 stop kidding
yourself that you're anything but meat
points PA F age 25 stop reading Charles
Bukowski points PA Tomkins age 18 stop
being dead for three years dogs
only Randazzo age 27 stop telling
everyone one you're an atheist we
know all right points PA F age
45 being relevant all right points
Randazzo age seven stop wetting the bed
points Randazzo age 67 start wetting the
bed
again
Randazzo age 81 stop referring to the
Irish as dirty potato
[Laughter]
Grandpa hman age 13 7 stop drinking the
blood of Orphans to replenish your
wretched life
force